globalpages.com 2009-06-23

# Privacy Policy, GlobalPages.com

Privacy Policy 

It is very important to us at Globalpages.com to ensure that this, and every subsequent visit you make to our website, is with complete peace of mind. You have every right to trust and to expect confidentiality, and we respect this right. 

Your privacy is our priority. As such, we believe you should have an overview of how we collect data about the people who visit our site and what we do with that data. The following are the policies that we have put in place to ensure such an environment at Globalpages.com

#### Use of Content

Every time you visit Globalpages.com, you may be providing some, even all, of the following information:

  * Anonymous information
  * Aggregate Data
  * Any personally identifiable information you knowingly provide us

If you are concerned about Globalpages.com or selling any personally identifiable information to any telemarketing, direct marketing or commercial mass email companies, agents or representatives, you should not. Because we will not do that. if you tell us it's okay to do so. Here are the only instances Globalpages.com could maybe, perhaps, possibly send personally identifiable information to other companies or people:

  * You have given Globalpages.com your explicit permission to share this information;
  * Globalpages.com needs to share the information to provide a product or service you requested;
  * If Globalpages.com believes, in good faith, that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal process;
  * If Globalpages.com finds that your actions on the Globalpages.com website violates the Globalpages.com Terms of Use or any of Globalpages.com's usage guidelines for specific products or services.

#### Disclaimers & Liability

At Globalpages.com, we collect information to provide more services and benefits to you.  We do not collect any personal information but what you did while you were visiting our website. 

This information provides Globalpages.com with valuable feedback which we use to improve both our site and our services. One good example: we can inform Globalpages.com advertisers how many people saw or clicked on their ads - plus, how many people saw or clicked on ads in different sections of our website. 

We also monitor information so that we can produce aggregate reports for internal use - and for use by third parties, including Globalpages.com advertisers. Aggregate reports are mostly statistical and deal with information like people behavior and number of total visits and page views not about individual behavior. 

From time to time we may release information about aggregate user characteristics, but we do not include any personally identifiable information about you or your individual online usage patterns.

Globalpages.com collects information about your site usage through cookies  and through our server log files, including IP Addresses. Please note that Globalpages.com does not link IP Addresses to any personally identifiable information.  With cookies, we can customize areas of 

Globalpages.com content according to your preferences. What's more, Cookies allow us to target our advertisements and limit the number of times you see pop-ups on our site. Cookies tell us nothing about you personally, unless of course you elect to give us additional information about yourself.

#### Opt Out!

You can always disable the cookie function if you so choose in your browsers settings. However, we can not guarantee that our website will work properly. You may lose the ability to use some of its advanced features at Globalpages.com.

Some of the banner and display ads on Globalpages.com are provided by third party ad servers. These ads may also contain cookies. Information collected through cookies associated with third party ads are collected by the third party and we do not always have access to this information. It is our policy, however, to only use reputable third parties with their own good privacy policies to serve the advertisements that are placed within our website.

#### Personal Data

If you order any products or services from Globalpages.com we will collect personally identifiable data from you in order to process the transaction and to provide you with the support and tools required to maintain and modify your directory listings.

We also collect personally identifiable data in other situations where you knowingly provide us with such information. For example, when you complete online surveys, participate in a sweepstakes or contest, or communicate with our Staff.

#### Your Security

Globalpages.com understands how important it is to protect you and your information. We take security seriously, online and offline. All sensitive information, including credit card details, is encrypted using the very latest server technology. Your browser should let you know when you are about to make a secure connection by an image of an unbroken key or a closed lock (as shown below) at the bottom corner of your browser. If the image is broken or open, your connection is not secure. From time to time, Globalpages.com may amend this policy to provide our visitors the latest tools and techniques being developed.
